screener.in 2019-06-11

# Guide - Screener

Last updated July 01, 2018

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at Mittal Analytics Private Limited, doing business as Screener.in ( **“Screener.in”** , **“we”** , **“us”** , or **“our”** ). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at screener.help@gmail.com.

When you visit our website https://www.screener.in, and use our services, you trust us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we describe our privacy policy. We seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy policy that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Sites and our services.

This privacy policy applies to all information collected through our website (such as https://www.screener.in), and/or any related services, sales, marketing or events (we refer to them collectively in this privacy policy as the "Sites").

Please read this privacy policy carefully as it will help you make informed decisions about sharing your personal information with us.

## 1\. What information do we collect?

**Information collected from other sources**

**In Short:** _We may collect limited data from public databases, marketing partners, and other outside sources._

We may obtain information about you from other sources, such as public databases and from other third parties. Examples of the information we receive from other sources include: social media profile information from social logins; search results and links, including paid listings (such as sponsored links).

## 2\. How do we use your information?

**In Short:** _We process your information for improving the services based on legitimate business interests, the fulfillment of our contract with you, compliance with our legal obligations, and/or your consent._

We use personal information collected via our Sites for a variety of business purposes described below. We process your personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests ("Business Purposes"), in order to enter into or perform a contract with you ("Contractual"), with your consent ("Consent"), and/or for compliance with our legal obligations ("Legal Reasons"). We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next to each purpose listed below.

We use the information we collect or receive:

  * **To facilitate account creation and logon process** with your Consent. If you choose to link your account with us to a third party account *(such as your Google or Facebook account), we use the information you allowed us to collect from those third parties to facilitate account creation and logon process.

  * **To send administrative information to you** for Business Purposes, Legal Reasons and/or possibly for Contractual. We may use your personal information to send you product, service and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.

  * **Fulfill and manage your orders** for Contractual reasons. We may use your information to fulfill and manage your orders, payments, returns, and exchanges made through the Sites.

  * **Request Feedback** for our Business Purposes and/or with your Consent. We may use your information to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Sites.

  * **To protect our Sites** for Business Purposes and/or for Legal Reasons. We may use your information as part of our efforts to keep our Sites safe and secure (for example, for fraud monitoring and prevention).

  * **To enforce our terms, conditions and policies** for Business Purposes, Legal Reasons and/or possibly Contractual.

  * **To respond to legal requests and prevent harm** for Legal Reasons. If we receive a subpoena or other legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond.

  * **For other Business Purposes.** We may use your information for other Business Purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Sites, products, services, marketing and your experience.

**In Short:** _We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations._

We only share and disclose your information in the following situations:

  * **Compliance with Laws.** We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).

  * **Vital Interests and Legal Rights.** We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

  * **Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers.** We may share your data with third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. Examples include: **payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service and marketing efforts.** We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Sites, which will enable them to collect data about how you interact with the Sites over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. Unless described in this Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

  * **Business Transfers.** We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

  * **With your Consent.** We may disclose your personal information for any other purpose with your consent.

## 4\. Do we use cookies and other tracking technologies?

**In Short:** _We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information._

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Policy.

## 5\. How long do we keep your information?

**In Short:** _We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless otherwise required by law._

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements). No purpose in this policy will require us keeping your personal information for longer than the period of time in which users have an account with us.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

## 6\. How do we keep your information safe?

**In Short:** _We aim to protect your personal information by using the best industry frameworks and through a system of organizational and technical security measures._

We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, please also remember that we cannot guarantee that the internet itself is 100% secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Sites is at your own risk. You should only access the services within a secure environment.

## 7\. Do we collect information from minors?

**In Short:** _We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 18 years of age._

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Sites, you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Sites. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at screener.help@gmail.com.

## 8\. What are your privacy rights?

**In Short:** _You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time._

**Account Information**

If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can:

  * Log into your account settings and update your user account.

  * Contact us using the contact information provided.

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements.

**Cookies and similar technologies:** Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Sites. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Sites visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.

**Opting out of emails:** You can unsubscribe from emails at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails that we send or by contacting us using the details provided below. You will then be removed from the emails list – however, we will still need to send you service-related emails that are necessary for the administration and use of your account. To otherwise opt-out, you may:

  * Access your account settings and update preferences.

  * Contact us using the contact information provided.

## 10\. Do we make updates to this policy?

**In Short:** _Yes, we will update this policy as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws._

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy policy frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

If you have questions or comments about this policy, you may email us at screener.help@gmail.com or by post to:

Mittal Analytics Private Limited  
1st Floor, Nikhilesh Palace,  
Ashok Marg,  
Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh 226001  
India

If you have any further questions or comments about us or our policies, email us at screener.help@gmail.com or by post to:

Mittal Analytics Private Limited  
1st Floor, Nikhilesh Palace,  
Ashok Marg,  
Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh 226001  
India
